

Dorđe VasićIT Business Analyst

Contact

Phone

- +381 60 546 0943
- +381 63 821 8306

E-mail

vasicdjordje@hotmail.com

Address:

Mitropolita Stratimirovića 74. 21205 Sremski Karlovci

Skills

Math

Advanced

Project Scheduling

Expert

Problem Solving

Expert

Multi-tasking

Expert

Quality reporting

<u>Advanced</u>

Languages

English

Advanced

IT Business Analist with over 8 years of IT software development experience in a Company that uses over 90 applications. Motivated by results, able to follow the entire application development process from analysis to implementation. Quickly learniner who can adapt to new environments, user requirements as well as new business systems.

Experience

2010-06- **IT Business analyst - Expert Associate Postal tehnology Engineer** 2019-08 Poste Srpske A.D. Banja Luka

- Complete monitoring of the SDLC and participating in all its stages.
- Detailed analysis of the manufacturing and technological processes of the Company and the creation of documented proposals for business and technical solutions (BRD / FSD).
- Involved in software monitoring and developer-tester collaboration.
- Communication with a wide range of employees in the Company who are involved in the implementation of the IT project and the work in Agile Software Development environment involving a large number of people.
- Making detailed business analysis and calculations, resolving problems, targeting
 opportunities and solutions for postal company that includes a wide range of
 services from transfer of goods to financial transfer and payment services.
- Finding ways to improve technical efficiency based on previous research.
 Definition and introducing of brand new services, as well as improvement of existing ones.
- Conducting meetings and Collaboration with other companies involved in the implementation of the IT project, IT company, Banks, suppliers and end users.
- Designing and writing technical and technological documentation.

Education

2017-2018

ITAcademy, Belgrade

Web Developer

2000-2007

Faculty of Technical Sciences, Novi Sad

MASTER of Postal traffic and telecommunications

Tehnical capability and competence

Technologies:

PHP, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, Apache

Coding patterns and CMS Systems:

React.js, Gatsby, GraphQL, Yii2, JQuery, Angular, Bootstrap, Wordpress, Joomla.

Designing Software:

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, InVision Studio, Corel Draw, Adobe Premiere, Dreamweaver.

Version control:

Git - GitHub

Other Software:

Microsoft Office Suite, MySQL Workbranch

Hobbies:

Karate master, Brazilian jiu-jitsu brown belt, coach and active competitor